E. P. Dutton & Company, Inc. Records
E. P. Dutton & Company, Inc. Records
- Publicity files
  - Phelps II (Box 50)
    Phelps, Prof. W. Lyon 1929
    Phelps, Prof. W. Lyon 1928
  - Phelps - Pierson (Box 50)
    Phelps, Prof. W. Lyon Biog., Items, & Photos
    Phelps, Prof. W. Lyon Correspondence
    Phelps, Prof. W. Lyon Reviews
    Phillips, Alexandra (Ruth)
    Phillips, Duncan
    Phillpatts, Eden
    Piccard, Professor
    Pierce, Dorothy 1933-1934
    Pierce, Fredrick Correspondence
    Pierson, Clara D.
  - Pinero - Pirandello (Box 50)
    Pinero, Sir Arthur Wing Correspondence
    Pirandello, Luigi Correspondence #1
    Pirandello, Luigi Correspondence #2
  - Pirandello I (Box 50)
    Pirandello, Luigi 1934
    Pirandello, Luigi 1932-1933
    Pirandello, Luigi 1929-1931
    Pirandello, Luigi Kennaday & Livingston, Inc. Curtis Brown
  - Pirandello II (Box 50)
    Pirandello, Luigi Nobel Prize Story & American Visit 1935
    Pirandello, Luigi Articles & Personal Items
    Pirandello, Luigi Reviews
  - Pirandello I, reviews and Clippings (Box 51)
  - Pirandello II, photos, reviews, clipping, articles, personal (Box 51)
  - Pirandello - Porte
    Pirandello
    Pitz, Henry C.
    Planck, Dr. Max
    Playfair, Giles
    Plowman, Max
    Pocock, Guy
    Pogany, Willy, illus.
    Polsky, Thomas
    Poliakov, A.
    Ponsonky, Arthur
    Pope, Mrs.
    Porte, John F.
  - Porter - Power (Box 51)
    Porter, Laura Spencer
    Posse-Brozadora, Amilie
    Potter, Miriam Clarke
    Pound, Ezra
    Power, Effie 1935
  - Power - Powers (Box 51)
    Power, Effie 1934
    Power, Effie 1928-1933
    Powers, John
  - Powys - Protheros (Box 51)
    Powers Girl Party
    Powys, Llewellyn
    Pratt, Theodore
    Pretice, Rev. Sartell
    Prescott W.H. (conquest of Mexico Illus. Ed.)
    Price, Mattack
    Pritchard, Virginia Cole
    Prodgers, C.H.
    Profit Sharing by American Employers
    Prosser, David
    Protherol, Ernest
  - Proulx - Raile (Box 51)
    Proulx, Benjamin A.
    Purdom, C.B.
    Pyle, Katherine 1916-1922
    Pyle, Katherine 1929
    Pyle, Katherine 1930's
    Pyle, Katherine Reviews
    Pyle, Katherine 1928
    Queena, Mario
    Rackham, Mario
    Radziwill, Princess
    Radcliffe, William
    Raile, Dr.
  - Rau - Reeve (Box 51)
    Rau, Neil & Margaret
    Rawson, Marion Nicholl
    Rawson, Marion Nicholl 1929-1935
    Read, Winwood Correspondence
    Read, Winwood Reviews
    Reece, Byron Herbert
    Reeve, Sidney
  - Reeve - Reynolds (Box 51)
    Reeve, Sidney A. 1933-1934
    Reeve, Sidney A. 1931-1932
    Reid, Leslie
    Rem, Henri
    Rentoul, Anne
    Reynolds, Quentin
  - Rhys - Robinson (Box 51)
    Rhys, Ernest Biog., Photos & Items
    Rhys, Ernest Correspondence
    Rhys, Ernest Reviews
    Rhys, Ernest 1929
    Rice, Conrad C.
    Ridley, M.R. Biog. & Items
    Ridley, M.R. Correspondence
    Ridley, M.R. Reviews
    Risenberg, Felix
    Ring, Anne
    River, W.S.
    Robb, Bernard
    Roberts, Morley Correspondence
    Roberts, Henry
    Robertson, Ale
    Robinson, Boardman
  - Robinson - Roughead (Box 51)
    Robinson, Gertrude
    Robinson, Iona
    Robinson, Lura
    Robinson, Mabel L. Correspondence
    Rochter, Olga
    Rogers, Prof. Lindsay Correspondence
    Roget, (Thesaurus)
    Rolland, Romain Report & Items
    Rolyat, Jane
    Roman, Frederick W.
    Romieu, Georges & Emile
    Roosevelt, Franklin Delano Correspondence
    Roper, Edith & Clara Leiser
    Rosrall, Toiro David
    Rose-Mathematics for Engineers
    Rosen, Dr. Friedrich
    Rothstein, John
    Rouge, Jean deVignes
    Roughead, William
  - Ruhl - Sassoon (Box 52)
    Rowell, Adeline C.
    Rubaiyat
    Ruhl, Arthur
    Russell, Bertrand
    Russell, Gilbert
    Ressell, Wm.
    St. Francis, Little Flower of
    Saint Jean, Robert de
    Saintbury, George Items
    Sampter, Miss.
    Sanger, Margaret
    Sassoon, Siegfried Correspondence
    Sassoon, Siegfried Reviews
  - Sassoon - Schwartz (Box 52)
    Sassoon, Siegfried Biog., Photos, & Items
    Satomi, Kisio
    Saunders, Wm.
    Sawyer, Charles J.
    Saxby, Charles
    Schem, Lida C. Correspondence
    Schlamm, Dr. Willi S.
    Schmidt, Peter
    Schniebs, Otto Eugen
    Schrenck-Notzing, Baron Correspondence
    Schriftgiesser, Karl
    Schriftgiesser, Karl Oscar of Waldorf
    Schulberg, Virginia
    Schwartz, E. Alexander
  - Schwartz - Scott (Box 52)
    Schwartz, Louis H.
    Schwartz, M.A.
    Scott, Cyril Correspondence
    Scott, Cyril Biog., Photos, etc.
    Scott, Mrs. Dawson
    Scott, R.T.
  - Scudder I (Box 52)
    Scudder, Vida Biog. & Photos
    Scudder, Vida 1930-1931
    Scudder, Vida Reviews
    Scudder, Vida Correspondence #1
    Scudder, Vida Correspondence #2
    Scudder, Vida Correspondence #3
  - Scudder II (Box 52)
    Scudder, Vida Correspondence #4
  - Selivanova - Sheehan (Box 52)
    Selivanova, Nina
    Sellar & Yeatman Reviews
    Semeonoff, Anna
    Serrage, Jane
    Sfoza, Count Correspondence
    Shanahan
    Shawn, Ted
    Sheahan, Gary
    Shedlock, Marie L. Correspondence & Items
    Sheeham, Munay Correspondence
  - Shelley - Sierra (Box 52)
    Shelley - Thomas L. Peacock et al Reviews
    Shelton, A.C.
    Shepard, E.H. Correspondence, Biog., & Photos
    Shepherd, Nan
    Shmelor, Ivan 1928-1934
    Shoemaker, Samuel
    Sieff, Mark
    Siegfried, Andre
    Sierra, Martinez Biog., Photos, & Items
  - Sierra - Sinclair (Box 52)
    Sierra, Martinez Correspondence
    Sierra, G.M.
    Sierra, G.M. Raget
    Sierra, Martinez Reviews
    Sim, Georges
    Simon, Charlie May Correspondence
    Simon, Charlie May
    Simons, Dr. Irving
    Simmons, Walter
    Sinclair, May Reports & Items
    Sinclair - Smith
    Sinclair, May Items
    Singh, J.
    Skomorowsky, Boris
    Slattery, Charles L.
    Sloane, Gertrude L.
    Sloss, Mrs. Hattie H.
    Small, Sidney
    Smallzried, Kathleen
    Smedley, Constsnce (Mrs. Maxwell Armfield)
    Smith, Andrew
    Smith, Mrs. Anna M.
    Smith, Bertha Whitridge
    Smith, Bertman
  - Smith (Box 52)
    Smith, George B.
    Smith, Gordon
    Smith, Lieut J.S.
    Smith, Laurence B. 1930-1934
    Smith, Laurence B.
    Smith, May Riley
  - Smith - Soddy (Box 53)
    Smith, Whately
    Smith, William B.
    Snell, George
    Snyder, Mrs. Milton V. (Alice Z.)
    Soddy, Sir Frederick Biog., Photos, & Items
    Soddy, Sir Frederick Correspondence
    Soddy, Sir Frederick Reviews
  - Sokoloff - Southard (Box 53)
    Sokoloff, Dr. Boris 1934
    Sokoloff, Dr. Boris
    Sommerfield, Arnold Biog. & Items
    Sommerfield, Arnold Correspondence
    Sommerfield, Arnold Reviews
    Sorokin, P.A. The Crisis of Our Age
    Sorokin, Prof. Pitirim Reviews
    Southard, Charles Z. Reviews
  - Southard - Stark (Box 53)
    Southard, Charles Z. Correspondence
    De Souza, Count Barretto 1927-1934
    Sowerbym G & M
    Spain, John
    Speare, Morris E.
    Speyer, Leonora Biog. & Photos
    Spurr, Archdeacon B.M.
    Stamp, L. Dudley
    Stopledon, Olof Old John Items
    Stark, Freya Biog., Photos, & Items
  - Stark - Steege (Box 53)
    Stark, Freya Reviews
    Starkie, Walter Reviews
    Starrett, Vincent
    Stebbins, Anna E.
    Steege, Mrs. Klyda R.
  - Steiner - Stillman (Box 53)
    Steiner - Theosophy
    Stendhal
    Stephenson, Nathaniel W.
    Sterling, Mary B.
    Stern, Madeline B.
    Sterner, Albert
    Stewart, Cora Wilson Correspondence
    Stewart, Wm. Rhinelander
    Stiles, Helen
    Stillman, Dorothea
  - Stimson - Strunsky (Box 53)
    Stimson, John L. (Henry A.) Correspondence
    Stries, Bishop Ernest M.
    Stitch, Wilhelmina
    Stork, Charles Wharton
    Stow, Edith
    Street, A.G.
    Street of Faces, The
    Strawbridge, Mrs. G.H.
    Strenkowsky - Serge
    Strong, Patience
    Strother, Mrs. E.V.
    Strunsky, Manya & Simeon Biog. & Obit.
    Strunsky, Simeon Correspondence
    Strunsky, Simeon
  - Stuart I (Box 53)
    Stuart, Jesse Reader's Reports of Mrs.
    Stuart, Jesse #1 Biog., Photos, & Items
    Stuart, Jesse #2 Biog., Photos, & Items
  - Stuart II (Box 53)
    Stuart, Jesse Reviews
    Stuart, Jesse Interviews & Stories (Personal)
  - Stuart III (Box 53)
    Stuart, Jesse Correspondence #1 1934
    Stuart, Jesse Correspondence #2 1935-1939
  - Studdy - Sylvin (Box 54)
    Stuart, Jesse Correspondence #3 1940-1946
    Studdy, G.E. & Jellicoe, George
    Sunbaltern on the Somme (Pub. Anon.)
    Sullivan, A.M.
    Suppervielle, Jules
    Sutton, Vida
    Summers, Montague
    Sward, Keith
    Sylvin, Frances
  - Symons (Box 54)
    Symons, Arthur Correspondence
    Symons, Arthur Biog., Photos, & Items
  - Taine - Tashlin (Box 54)
    Taine, John
    Talbot, E.A.
    Tamas, Istran
    Tashilin, Frank
    Tauheuhaus, Prof. J.J. Correspondence
    Tashlin, Frank
  - Tashlin - Taubenhaus (Box 54)
    Tashlin, Frank Bear That Wasn't - Christmas
    Tate, Alfred
    Taubenhaus, J.J. (Tanquery, M.C.)
  - Taubes - Tchernavin (Box 54)
    Taubes, Fredrick
    Taues, Isabella Miller
    Taylor, Griffith
    Tchernavin, Tatiana 1934-1935
    Tchernavin, Tatiana Articles and Items
    Tchernavin, Tatiana
    Tchernavin, Tatiana Biog., Photos, & Items
  - Tchernavin - Thomas (Box 54)
    Tchernavin, Tatiana Reviews
    Teale, Edwin Way Biog.
    Teall, Gardner
    Temple - Ellis, M.A. Curtis Brown, Ltd.
    Teuggrea, Gustof
    Thayer, Mary D.
    The Theolosophical Movement
    Thirkield, Wilbur P. and Oliver Huckel 1932-1934
    Thirkield, Wilbur P. and Oliver Huckel
    Thomas, C. Drayton
    Thomas, Lowell
  - Thomas - Thompson (Box 54)
    Thomas, Mrs. Theodore
    Thompson, Carl D.
    Thompson, Carl D. 1933-1934
    Thompson, Carl D. 1932
  - Thompson, Carl D. - Thompson, H.M. (Box 54)
    Thompson, Mrs. Charles D. (Mary)
    Thompson, Edward McCray
    Thompson, Edward Biog., Photos, & Items
    Thompson, Edward Correspondence
    Thompson, Edward Reviews
    Thompson, Grace E.
    Thompson, Hugh Miller (Bishop)
  - Thompson (Box 54)
    Thompson, Vance Correspondence #1
    Thompson, Vance Correspondence #2
  - Thompson - Tomlinson (Box 54)
    Thompson, Vance Reviews
    Thomson, J. Arthur Biog., Photos, & Items
    Thomson, J. Arthur Reviews
    Thorne, Harold 1933-1934
    Thornhill, J.B.
    Timlow, Elizabeth
    Tolstoi, Leo
    Tompkins, Floyd W.
    Tomlinson, H.M.
  - Tomlinson - Tracy (Box 54)
    Tomlinson, H.M. Reviews
    Toksvig, Signe
    Tompkins, Ellen Wilkins
    Tracy, Henry C. 1932-1934
    Tracy, Henry C. 1931
    Tracy, Henry C. 1930
    Tracy, Henry C. 1929
    Tracy, Henry C. 1928
  - Tracy - Truax (Box 55)
    Tracy, Henry Chester Biog. & Items
    Tracy, Henry Chester Comments
    Tracy, Henry Chester Reviews
    Tracy, Henry Chester Reviews - Towards the Open
    Trager, Mrs.
    Triem, Eve
    Truax, Rhoda (Mrs. Aldrich)
  - Truax - The Twelve Hour Day in American Industry (Box 55)
    Truax, Rhoda 1932-1934
    Tsanoff, Prof. R.A.
    Tuell, Annie K.
    Turner, Mrs. Horold
    Turner, John Hastings
    Turner, W.J. Correspondence
    Tweedale, Rev. C.L. Correspondence
    Twelve Hour Shift in American Industry Correspondence
  - Underhill (Box 55)
    Underhill, John Garret Correspondence
    Underhill, John Garret Correspondence #1
  - Vallee - Van Ammers-Kuller (Box 55)
    Vallee, Rudy
    Vaile, P.A.
    Van Ammers-Kuller, Jo Reader's Report
    Van Ammers-Kuller, Jo Correspondence
    Van Ammers-Kuller, Jo 1932
    Van Ammers-Kuller, Jo 1931
  - Van Ammers-Kuller (Box 55)
    Van Ammers-Kuller, Jo 1930
    Van Ammers-Kuller, Jo 1929
  - Van Ammers-Kuller - Vanden Berg (Box 55)
    Van Ammers-Kuller, Jo 1928
    Vance, Louis Joseph Biog., Photos, etc.
    Vance, Louis Joseph Correspondence
    Vandegrift, Georg Wonson
    Venden Berg, George
  - Van Doun - Vassos (Box 55)
    Van Doren, Carl
    Van Dyke, Henry Correspondence
    Van Dyke, Henry
    Van Eps, F.S. and M.B.
    Van Santroord, Seymour
  - Vassos - Verrill (Box 55)
    Vassos, John and Ruth Correspondence
    Vassos, John
    Vassos, John Review Solome
    Vassos, John Review Ultimo
    Vassos, John and Ruth
  - Verrill - Waite (Box 55)
    Ventilation Commission (N.Y.) Report
    Venturi, Leonello
    Vendery, Eleanor
    Verrill, A. Hyatt Correspondence & Items
    Verrill, A. Hyatt Correspondence
    Verrill, A. Hyatt Reader's Report
    Victoria Co. Hist. Of England
    Vidal, Gore
    Von Hutten Bowners
    Voronoff, Dr. Serge Correspondence
    Wade, George Woosung
    Wade, Rosalind
    Wadia, A.R.N.
    Waoenknecht, Edward
    Wain, Louis
    Waite
  - Waldman - Wallis (Box 55)
    Waldman, Louis
    Waldo, Fullerton L.
    Walker, Norman
    Walker, Kenneth & Boumphrey, Geoffrey
    Walkins Rhyming Dictionary
    Wallace, Edna Kingsley
    Walling, Wm. English Correspondence
    Wallis, J.H.
  - Wallis (Box 55)
    Wallis, J.H. 1933
    Wallis, J.H. 1930-1932
  - Walsh - Washington (Box 56)
    Walsh, Gertrude
    Walsh, Dr. Wm. S.
    Walton, Eda Lou
    Ward, Florence
    Ward, Mary Jane Biog., Photos, Items
    Ward, Mary Jane Reviews
    Warfield, Wallace Photos
    Waring, A.L.
    Warner, Oliver
    Warren, C. Henry
    Washington, Dr. John E.
  - Watson - Webb (Box 56)
    Watson, Frederick Photos & Items
    Wattles, Willard
    Wawn, Frank Correspondence & Items
    Wawn, F.T. Correspondence
    We Indians
    Webb, Mary Curtis Brown, Ltd.
    Webb, Mary Articles/Personal Items
    Webb, Mary Reviews
  - Webb (Box 56)
    Webb, Mary Biog., Photos, & Items
    Webb, Mary Correspondence 1916-1947
  - Webb - Wheeler (Box 56)
    Webb, Mary Reader's Reports
    Webb, Mary Fifty-Two Poems (1946)
    Webster, James
    Wheeler, Upal Sing For Christmas
  - Wheeler - Webster (Box 56)
    Wheeler, Upal Sing For America
    Wheeler, Upal Sing For Mother Goose
    Wheeler, Upal Items
    Wheeler, Upal Ludwig Beethoven
    Webster, Nesta Biog. & Items
    Webster, Nesta Correspondence
    Webster, Nesta Reviews
  - Weekly - Wells (Box 56)
    Weekly, Ernest Biog. & Photos
    Weekly, Ernest Correspondence
    Weekly, Ernest Correspondence & Items
    Weekly, Ernest Reviews
    Weeks, Raymond
    Weigall, Arthur
    Wellman, Walter
    Wells, G.R.
    Wells, H.G. Correspondence #1
  - Wells - Westrate (Box 56)
    Wells, H.G. Correspondence #2
    Wells, H.G. Items
    Wells, Maie Lounsbury
    Welshimer, Helen
    Wendel, Dr. F.C.H.
    Westrate, Edwin V.
  - Weyl - Wheeler (Box 56)
    Weyl, Dr. H.
    Wheaton, Elizabeth Lee Biog., Photos, etc.
    Wheaton, Elizabeth Lee Reviews
    Wheatley, Vera
    Wheeler, Everett P.
    Wheeler, Mrs. J.C. (Zoe B.)
    Wheeler, Keith
  - Wheeler - White (Box 56)
    Wheeler, Keith We Are The Wounded
    Wheeler, Post
    Whiffen, Mrs. Thomas
    White, Alice & Tobitt
  - White (Box 56)
    White, Edward Lucas Correspondence
  - White I (Box 57)
    White, Edward Lucas Correspondence #1
    White, Edward Lucas Reviews
    White, Edward Lucas 1932
    White, Edward Lucas 1931
    White, Edward Lucas 1930
  - White II (Box 57)
    White, Edward Lucas 1929
    White, Edward Lucas 1928
    White, Edward Lucas 1933
    White, Edward Lucas 1934
    White, Stewart Edward
  - White - Whittaker (Box 57)
    White, Gilbert
    Whiting, Gertrude
    Whiting, Lillian
    Whittaker, Lieut. James C.
  - Wilcke - Wilkins (Box 57)
    Wilcke, Eva
    [Wilder, James]
    [Wilkins, Harold T.]
  - Will - Williams, B. A. (Box 57)
    Will, Allen Correspondence
    Will, Allen (Life of Cardinal Gibbons) Correspondence & items
    Willcox, Mrs.
    William of Sweden, Prince
    Williams, Albert Rhys
    Williams, Ben Ames Reviews
    Williams, Ben Ames Biog., photos and items
    Williams, Ben Ames Correspondence #1
    Williams, Ben Ames Correspondence #2
  - Williams, B.A. I, 1932-1940 (Box 57)
  - Williams, B.A. II, 1928-1934 (Box 57)
  - Williams, R. - Williams, W. (Box 57)
    Williams, Rebecca Y. 1939-1940
    Williams, Rebecca Y. Items
    Williams, Stanley T.
    Williams, Trayne
    Williams, W. W.
    Williams, Wythe Correspondence #1
    Williams, Wythe Correspondence #2
  - Williamson I (Box 57)
    Wiiliamson, Henry 1935-1940
    Wiiliamson, Henry 1932-33-34
    Wiiliamson, Henry Readers reports
    Wiiliamson, Henry 1929
  - Williamson II (Box 57)
    Williamson, Henry Correspondence I
  - Williamson III (Box 57)
    Williamson, Henry Reviews
    Williamson, Henry 1931
    Williamson, Henry 1930
    Williamson, Henry The Pathway (1938?)
  - Williamson - Wilson (Box 58)
    Williamson, Henry Correspondence #1 (1923-1928)
    Willis, F. Milton
    Williston
    Wilson, David Alec Biog. & Photos
    Wilson, D.A. I Reviews of the Carlisle Books
    Wilson, D.A.
  - Wilson - Winters (Box 58)
    Wilson, D.A. II Reviews of the Carlyle Books
    Wilson, Eleanore Hubbard
    Wilson, Rev. Henry B.
    Wilson, John Fleming
    Wilton, Robert (Russia's Agony) Correspondence
    Wimberly, Lowry C.
    Wimberly, Pearl K.
    Winslav, C.E.A. Dr.
    Winters, Edgar S.
    Winters, Joseph E.
  - Wise - Wolff (Box 58)
    Wise, James Waterman 1928-1940
    Withers, Hartley Correspondence & Items
    Withers, Hartley Correspondence
    Withington, Alfreda April
    Witkop, Philipp
    Wolff, Werner
  - Wood (Box 58)
    Wood, Clement Correspondence
    Wood, Edith Elmer
  - Wood - Wright (Box 58)
    Wood, Lindsay Lemax
    Woodbridge, Grace Stone
    Woodbury, David O.
    Woodcock, Louise P. - Barbara Bibur
    Woodhouse, Henry
    Woodward, W.E.
    Worth, Cedric
    Wright, Constance
    Wright, Richardson
  - Wylie - Yaznik (Box 58)
    Wylie, I.A.R. Biog. & Correspondence
    Wynner, Edith
    Yank Anthology
    Weda Yap
    Yaznik, Dr. R.K.
  - Young (Box 58)
    Young, Col. G.F. Reports and Reviews
    Young, Col. G.F. Correspondence
    Young, Ella
    Young, Francis Brett Corres. #1 (1918-1922)
    Young, Francis Brett Corres. #2 (1923-1936)
    Young, Francis Brett Biog., Photos, & Items
  - Young (Box 58)
    Young, Francis Brett - Articles & Special Column
    Young, Francis Brett "Literary Notes"
    Young, Michael
  - Young - Zolotow (Box 58)
    Young, Owen D.
    Young, Evangeline W.
    Younghusband, Sir Francis Correspondence
    Youngs, Mary Frances
    Zamiatin (#2)
    Zolotow, Maurice
  - A (misc.) - Aldanov (Box 58)
    A (misc.)
    Admams, Dr. Clifford R.
    Adams, Joan
    Adams, Frank Davis
    Aldanor, Mark
  - Alexander - Anderson (Box 58)
    Alexander, Michael
    Alexander, Dr. Rolf
    Allfrey, P. Shand (Phyllis)
    Altrocchi, Julia Cooley
    Anderson, Kenneth
    Anderson, Patrick
    Anderson, William Ashley
  - Angle - Armstrong (Box 59)
    Angle, Paul M.
    Amory, Cleveland
    Andrzeyerski, George
    Andrews, Allen
    Anstruther, Ian
    Armstrong, R.L. Jr.
  - Arnothy - Asquith (Box 59)
    Arnothy, Christine
    Ashe, Geoffery
    Arnold, Lewis
    Asquith, Lady Cynthia
  - Aurobindo - Ayrton (Box 59)
    Aurobindo, Sri
    Ayrton, Elisabeth
  - B (misc.) (Box 59)
    B (misc.) Ba-Bn
    B (misc.) Bo-Bz
  - Bacal - Balchen (Box 59)
    Bacal, Jaques and Sloane, Louise
    Bacon, Edgar S. D.D.S.
    Bailey, Douglas Fields
    Baines, Frank
    Baker, Sherman BRADFORD MASTERS
    Balchen, Bernt
  - Baldwin - Barbour (Box 59)
    Baldwin, William
    Balliett, Whitney
    Ballard, James
    Barbour, Harriot Buxton
  - Barclay - Baron (Box 59)
    Barclay, Daphe
    Barnes, Henry A.
    Baron, A.L. (Abraham Louis)
  - Barrie - Basic Bible (Box 59)
    Barrie, J.M.
    Barrymaine, Norman
    Basic Bible
  - Basic Bible - Bassan (Box 59)
    The Basic Bible
    Basinsky, Earle, Jr.
    Bassan, Jean
  - Basseches - Beer (Box 59)
    Basseches, Nikolaus
    Bate, H. Maclear
    Bauer, W.W. and Edgley, Leslie
    Beer, Ethel S.
    Beerm Sir Gavin de
  - Beirne - Bendit (Box 59)
    Beirne, Francis F.
    Bell, Mary Hayley
    Bell, Peggy Kirk
    Bell, Sam Hanna
    Bendit, L.J. and Payne, Phoebe D.
  - Benedictus - Bennett (Box 60)
    Benedictus, David
    Bennett, Margot
  - Bentley - Berenstain (Box 60)
    Bentley, Nicolas
    Bentz, Hans G.
    Benuzzi, Felice
    Berenstain, Stanley and Janice
  - Berger - Berriman (Box 60)
    Berger, Oscar
    Berriault, Gina
    Berriman, A.E.
  - Berson (Box 60)
    Berson, Minnie Penin
  - Bertranet - Bischof (Box 60)
    Bertranet, Yves
    Bestic, Albert A.
    Bettemann, Otto L.
    Bisch, Jorgen
    Bischoff, Werner
  - Bloodgood - Bonavia-Hunt (Box 60)
    Bloodgood, Lide Fleitmann and Santini, Piero
    Bode, Carl
    Bonavia-Hunt, D.A.
  - Bouisson - Bo (Box 60)
    Bouisson, Maurice
    Boulnois, Luce
    Boyd, Martin
    Box, Edgar
  - Boyd (Box 60)
    Boyd, Maj. Gen. Albert
    Boyd, T.A. Professional Amateur
  - Boyd - Brady (Box 60)
    Boyd, T.A.
    Brady, Charles A.
  - Brady - Brinkley (Box 60)
    Brady, Leo
    Briggs, Martin S.
    Bridges, Lucas
    Brinkley, William
  - Briscoe - Browning (Box 60)
    Brooks, Ewart
    Brown, Ivor
    Brown, John
    Brown, Will C. (C.S. Boyles, Jr.)
    Browne, Douglas; Tullett, E.V. and Brock, Alan
    Browning, Robert
  - Bruff - Buckingham (Box 61)
    Bruff, Nancy
    Buchanan, Lamont
    Buckingham, Nadia and Etter, Ingrid
  - Buetow - Bernett (Box 61)
    Buetow, Rev. Harold A.
    Buhl, Harman
    Burnett, Whit and Hallie
  - Bush - C (misc.) (Box 61)
    Bush, Warren
    Butler, E.M. (Eliza Marian)
    CA - CO (misc.)
    CO (misc.)
  - Caesar - Cacopardo (Box 61)
    Caesar, Gene
    Cabries, Jacob
    Cacopardo, Rev. J.Jerry and Weldon, Don
  - Caley - Campbell (Box 61)
    Caley, Hanri
    Campanis, Al
    Campbell, Dorcas Your Career in Banking
  - Campbell - Carnegie (Box 61)
    Campbell-Johnson, Alan
    Carmer, Carl
    Carnegie (Dorothy) Mrs. Dale
  - Carpenter - Carlson (Box 61)
    Carpenter, Ralph E., Jr.
    Carr, Glyn
    Carlson, John Roy The Plotters
  - Carswell - Chase (Box 61)
    Carswell, John
    Caulfield, M.F.
    Champion, Selwyn Gurney
    Charques, Richrd
    Chase, James Hadley
  - Chilsote - Church (Box 61)
    Chilcote, Thomas E.
    Church, Richard
  - Churchill - Clark (Box 61)
    Churchill, Allen
    Cianfarra, Camille M.
    Ciano, Count
    Clarck, Brigadier Stanley
  - Claytor - Cleveland (Box 61)
    Claytor, Gerturde Boatwright
    Clebertm Jean-Paul
    Cleveland, Anne and Anderson, Jean
  - Clewes - Cohen (Box 61)
    Clewes, Howard
    Clewes, Winston
    Clifford, Francis
    Clifford, Henry V.C.
    Cohen, Abraham
  - Coleman - Collans (Box 62)
    Coleman, Lonnie
    Colin, Paul
    Cohen, Israel (also see Paul Goodman in Gompers - Goddin, Box 64)
    Collans, Dev with Stewart Sterling
  - Collier - Conerly (Box 62)
    Collier, Eric
    Collis, Maurice
    Colquhoun, Archibald
    Conerly, Charlie
  - Conil - Considine (Box 62)
    Conil, Jean
    Connolly, Francis X
    Conrad, Jack Randolph
    Considine, Bob
  - Cooke - Coon (Box 62)
    Cooke, David C.
    Coppel, Alec
    Coon, Horace
  - Cooper - Corle (Box 62)
    Cooper, Duff (Viscount Norwich)
    Cooper, Mae
    Corcoran, Austin and Corey, M.J.
    Corle, Edwin
  - Corredor - Cotton (Box 62)
    Corredor, J. Ma.
    Cotton, Emmi
  - Cottman - Cronyn (Box 62)
    Cottman, Evans W. and Balssingame, Wyatt
    Coxhead, Nona
    Cronyn, George W.
  - Cross - Crowther (Box 62)
    Crossen, Kendell Foster (Monig)
    Crowther, Bosley
  - Cugle - Cunningham (Box 62)
    Cugle, Charles H. and Stephens, I.J.
    Cunningham, Admiral
  - D (misc.) - Daniel-Rops (Box 62)
    D (misc.)
    Daley, Arthur
    Daniel-Rops
  - Davidson - Dempsey (Box 62)
    Davidson, Dr. Martin
    Davis, Richard Beale
    Dean, James E.
    Dean, Robert and George
    Delderfield, R.F.
    Dempsey, David
  - Dent - Derval (Box 62)
    Dent, J.M.
    Denzer, Peter W.
    Derval, Paul
  - Deutsch - Divine (Box 63)
    Deutsch, Babette
    Dingle, John
    Dior, Christian
    Divine, A.D.
  - Dogbolt - Douglas (Box 63)
    Dogbolt, Barnaby (Dr. Henry Silvette)
    Dodson, Daniel B.
    Doncaster, Patrick
    Douglas, Donald
  - Douglas-Home - Druon (Box 63)